const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the square of 4?",
        answer: "16",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is the cube root of 27?",
        answer: "3",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is square of 11?",
        answer: "121",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is 5 * 6?",
        answer: "30",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What is 10 / 2?",
        answer: "5",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What is square of 12?",
        answer: "144",

    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What is cube of 5?",
        answer: "125",

    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What is square root of 81?",
        answer: "9",

    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is square of 10?",
        answer: "100",

    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is cube of 3?",
        answer: "27",

    },
];

export default questions;
